Hello.
こんにちは
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
We finally met.
やっと会えたね
I was surprised.
びっくりした
So cute.
かわいくて
Have you ever been told that you want to be an idol?
アイドルにいそうとか言われない?
Not told.
言われない
What kind of system is it called?
何系って言われる?
Who do you look like?
誰に似てるとか
Maybe I've never been told that.
言われたことないかも
It looks like something like Nogizaka or something like that.
何かああいうのぎ坂とか、 そっち系にいそう
No, no, no.
違う違う違う
I like this bag next to my nose.
この 袋いいね、鼻の横に
I really don't like it.
結構嫌だもんね
It's cute.
かわいいやん
If you want to get the bag, you can.
袋取りたかったら取れるよ
I took the one that was on the top of my nose.
鼻のてっぺんにあったやつ取ったし
Wow, points.
すごい、ポイント
Did you pay 5,000 yen?
5000円とかやったでしょ?
or
や
water.
す い
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいるの?
Who do you like?
好きな人は?
There's no one I like.
好きな人もいない
How long have you been gone, boyfriend?
いつからいないの、彼氏
About a year ago.
1年前くらい
Which side did it come from?
それはどっち側から生き出したの?
We're both getting colder now.
もうお互い寒くなっちゃって
Well, that's fine, not yet.
じゃあいいやんね、まだ
It would be painful if one side was cold while the other was extremely hot.
片方冷めてるのに、 片方めっちゃ熱あるやつだったら辛いけど
If you do both.
両方やったらね
Don't you have anything to eat?
食いもないの?
There isn't.
ないの
At what point do you think, Wow, this guy doesn't exist?
どういうところで、 うわ、こいつないわってなる?
We're dating.
付き合ってて
Should I apply to be a store clerk?
店員さんに応募とか?
One of them might end up throwing away something.
片方なんか、ポイ捨てしちゃうとか
No, that's it.
いや、それね
What about walking cigarettes?
歩きタバコは?
Not many people smoke.
タバコを吸ってる人があんまりいない
I really hate it when I don't smoke while walking.
歩きタバコしないとほんまに嫌い
I don't smoke either.
俺も吸わへんから
I don't dislike it.
嫌 いない
It's just a nuisance.
迷惑でしかないやん
I'm a student.
私、学生やんか
Has your partner ever dated a working person?
相手が社会人と付き合ったことある?
Maybe not.
ないかもしれない
Sometimes I ask about myself, the students, the other person,
たまに聞くのが、私、学生、相手、
social person.
社会人
But it's not my fault, I guess.
でも悪いかん、みたいな
all.
すべて
What do you think about that?
それはどう思う?
He's a good boy.
いい子やね
Ecchi, it’s been a while hasn’t it?
えっち、久々じゃない?
boyfriend.
彼氏
What do you dislike?
どういうのが嫌とか、逆
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
Is it the flirty type, or do you call it cracking?
イチャイチャ系か、 バチボコって言うのかな?
To put it in a modern way.
今風に言うと
Which one do you like?
どっちが好き?
I don't like the pain, so I'd rather make out.
痛いの嫌だから、イチャイチャの方が
Bullying such a cute girl is scary.
こんな可愛い子いじめろ、怖い
We're having a lot of fun.
いっぱいイチャイチャしょうなの
Shit is cute too.
クソも可愛いね
My stomach is growling.
お 腹鳴っちゃう
It makes my stomach growl quite a bit.
結構お腹鳴るよね
If you really care.
あんま気になると
When I feel like that, my stomach starts growling.
そんな気になると、お腹鳴っちゃう
I'm curious.
気になるね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What should I do?
どうしよう
Is there something missing?
なかすいてる?
It's not burning.
やくない
I can't help it.
仕方ない
You can see it there.
あそこ見られるの
amazing.
すごい
Probably the most embarrassing.
たぶん一番恥ずかしい
Double and embarrassing.
ダブルで恥ずかしい
My stomach grumbles when I hide it.
隠すとこお腹鳴る
I thought my stomach might growl.
お腹鳴っちゃうかも、と思って
I'm nervous.
緊張してるな
The way he takes off his clothes is like a child's.
脱ぎ方が、子供みたいな脱ぎ方してる
I'm going to Moro.
モロに行っちゃう
cute.
可愛い
I'm fine after all.
やっぱり元気だ
I'm fine, stomach.
元気だ、お腹
Were you able to relieve your tension?
緊張解けできた?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I don't like it, don't play.
嫌だ、遊ばないで
Is it difficult to maintain your position?
体勢やりにくい?
Wash your feet.
足洗う
Is it refreshing?
すっきりした?
I was sweating.
汗かいたもんね
I was sweating a lot.
めっちゃ汗かいた
I'm sweating and my stomach is growling.
汗かくし、お腹ぐうぐう鳴るし
I hate it, my stomach.
嫌だ、お腹
cute.
可愛 い
I don't know what to look at when it comes to how men work.
男の仕組みってどこなん見ていいか分かんない
I don't know.
分かんない
I hate that, you know.
嫌うね、それね
beautiful.
綺麗
That's a strange way to hold it.
変わった持ち方ですね
変 わ った 持 ち 方 ですね
That's right.
そうよ